Financial Secretary; Records ua305
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Financial Secretary Records
1844-1965
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State College for Teachers (Albany, N.Y.)
ua305
15.2 cubic ft.
This collection consists primarily of the records of the Treasurer for the State College for Teachers. Also included are some financial records from earlier iterations of the College (New York State Normal School and New York State Normal College) and records of the Financial Secretary, which succeeded the position of Treasurer. Materials include cash books, budget documents, and correspondence.
Biographical History
The first Financial Secretary for the New York State College for Teachers, Clarence Joseph Deyo, was hired in 1917 and served until approximately 1945. His position title soon changed to "Secretary-Treasurer" but "Financial Secretary" was adopted by his successors in the 1940s through 1960s: Ainard Gelbond and Benjamin Comi. This position transitioned to the Director of Business Affairs, which itself eventually came under the umbrella of the Vice President for Management and Planning as the organization of the University became more complex. The Financial Secretary (or Secretary-Treasurer) was responsible for all aspects of the College's finances: receipts and disbursements, tuition, and payroll.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes: cash books and ledgers; correspondence with State agencies; budget planning documentation; payroll information; Special Fund receipts and disbursements; scholarship data and related correspondence; and other finance-related reports and correspondence. Information pertains to both the New York State College for Teachers and the Milne school that was overseen by the college.The bulk of these materials were created by Clarence Deyo during his term as Secretary-Treasurer from 1917 until 1945.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection arranged into 2 series. Series 1 is unprocessed and Series 2 is only partially processed, so individual items may be difficult to find.
Acquisition Information
Items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives. Undated
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Budget; Budget process; Education, Higher--Administration; Payrolls; Administrative records; payroll records; Financial Records; UAlbany Finance & Business; State University of New York at Albany
- Administrative Records, 1928-1953; 1; 10 cubic ft. (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10)
  Arrangement
  Series is arranged in its original order. This series was processed in August 2017 and was maintained in the state it was found. Within this series there are file series that can be found, usually related to each by the same general date. Some folders that were in poor condition have been replaced.
  Scope and Contents
  Contains budget records, administrative correspondence, receipts and disbursements, tuition records, and other records related to financial management.
  - R57 Rent Ridgefield, 1936 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - R59 Round Table Expenses, 1936 April 10-1936 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - S61 Misc, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - S61 Scholarships, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - S61 Scholarship Montgomery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - S62 Service Records and Ratings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - S64 Simpson Dr. A.D., 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - S65 Special Funds, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - S65 Special Funds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - S65 Spelman Budget, 1936 May 1-1936 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - S66 Student-Fed. Aid, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - S67 Loan Funds Student, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Teachers Retirement, 1937 October 27-1937 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - T69 Temporary Emer. Maint., Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - T70 Trans of Records, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - T70 Misc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - T70 Tuition- M.H.S., 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - V71 Misc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - V72 Misc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - W73 Misc., 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Acknowledgements, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Aa-Al 1, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Am-Ar 2, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ashes and Snow Removal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Baa-Bar 4, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bas-Baz( to Bz) 5, 1930 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Be( to Bh) 6, 1930 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bo(to Bq) 8, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bra-Bri(to Brn) 9, 1930 March 13-1930 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bro-Bry(to Bt) 10, 1930 March 7-1930 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bu-By(to Bz) 11, 1930 March 1-1930 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ca(to Cd) 12, 1930 March 3-1930 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Carpenters Correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clock System, 1930 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Ce-Ci-Cl(to Cn) 13, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Coa-Con 14, 1930 April 10-1930 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Connecting Corridors, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Coo-Coz(to Cq) 15, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cr(to Ct) 16, 1930 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Civil Service Commission, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Da-De(to Dh) 18, 1930 April 3-1930 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Dept. of Printing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Dayo Treasurer,C.J., Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Di-Do(to Dq) 19, 1930 March 1-1930 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Dr-Du-Dy(to Dz) 20, 1929 November 23 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ea-En 21, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Fencing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Fa-Fe-Fi(to Fk), 1930 March 1-1930 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Forms Office Record, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Fl-Fo(to Fq), 1930 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Floors, Polishing and Sanding, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Fr-Fu-Fy(to Fz), 1930 July 11-1930 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Ga-Ge(to Gh), 1930 February 1-1930 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Gi-Gl-Go(to Gq), 1930 May 6-1930 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Gr-Gy(to Gz), 1930 June 2-1930 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Haa-Han(to Haq), 1930 April 1-1930 September 3 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Har-Hay(to Hd), 1930 March 3-1930 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Hi(to Hn), 1930 April 3-1930 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ho(to Ht), Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Hu-Hy(to Hz), 1930 May 22-1930 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - I, Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Inventory, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Inventory, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Injury to Persons or Property, Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - J, 1930 April 4-1930 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Ki-Ko(to Kq), 1930 March 1-1930 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - La(to Ld), 1930 March (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Laws of N.Y. State, 1930 January 29-1930 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Le(to Lh), 1930 March 31-1930 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Library Shelving, Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Li-Ll-Ly(to Lz), Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - McE-McK, 1930 June 2-1930 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - McL-McZ, 1930 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Ma(to Md), Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Me-Mi(to Mn), 1930 March 3-1930 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Mo-Mu(to Mx), Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Na-Ne-Ni(Nn), Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - No-Ny(to Nz), 1930 April 1-1930 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - O, 1930 April 30-1930 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Orders, Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Pa-Pe(to Ph), Undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Paycheck, Bi-Monthly, Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Pi-Pl-Po(to Pq), Undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Pr-Py(to Pz), Undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Q, 1929 June 17-1930 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Ra-Re(to Rh), 1930 January 21-1930 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Repairs General, Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Repairs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Repairs Home Dinning Room, Undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Rog-Ruz(to Rz), Undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Sa-Sca(to Sog), Undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Sch-Scy(to Sd), Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Shop Equipment Etc., 1930 March 6-1930 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Si-Smi(Sn), 1930 March 4-1930 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Dr. A.D. Simpson, Undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Inventory, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Orders - Baker & Taylor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pa-Pe(to Ph), Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pi-Pl-Po(to Pq), Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Practice Teaching Cards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pr-Py(to Pz), 1929 December 7-1930 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Q, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Requests from all Depts., Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ra-Re(to Rh), 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Retirement System, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ri-Rod(to Rof), 1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rules and Regulations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rog-Ruz(to Rz), 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sa-Sca(to Sog), Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Rood Repairs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sch-Scy(to Sd), Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Se-Sha(to Shd), Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - She-Shy(to Shz), 1931 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Si-Smi(Sn), 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Simpson, A.D., Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Simpson, A.D., Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Special Fund Est. Monthly Report Blanks, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - So-Sp-Sq(to Ss), 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Special Fund Reports, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Laura Spellman Rockefeller Fund, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Stenographers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Special Fund, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sta-Ste(to Sth), Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Sti-Sty(to Stz), Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Su-Sy(to Sz), Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Temporary Emergency Relief, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ta-Te-Ti(to Tn), Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - To-Tr-Tu(to Tz), 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - U, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - V, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Wa(to Wd), Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - We(to Wg), Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Wia-Will, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Wim-Wiz(to Wn), 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Wo-Wz, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Y(Inc. X), Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Milne School Budget Request, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Special Fund Report, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Special Fund Report: Jan.1943-Dec. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Special Fund Report: Jan.1943-Dec. 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Special Fund Report: Jan. 1944-Dec.1944 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Special Fund Report: Jan. 1945-Jan. 1947, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Special Fund Report: Jan. 1947-Jun.1948, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Aa-Al 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A2 Analysis of Expenditures, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - A2 Appropriations, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Am-Ar 2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A3 Ashes +Snow, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - As-Az 3, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Baa-Bar 4, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - B4 Banker + Taylor, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - B4 Barnes + Noble, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bas-Bd 5, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - B7 Bills from Legislature, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bi-Bn 7, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - B7 Binding Books etc., Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bo-Bq 8, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bro-Bt 10, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bu-Bz 11, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - B11-Budget File, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - C12 Career Bill, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ca-Cd 12, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ce-Cn 13, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Coa-Con 14, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Coo-Cq 15, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Cr-Ct 16, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Cu-Cz 17, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - D18 Dept. Civil Service, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - D18 Dept. of Correction, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - D18 Dept. of Taxation + Finance, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Da-Dh 18, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - D18 Dept. Architecture, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - D18 Dept. Audit + Control, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - D18 Deposits, National Commercial Bk, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - D18 Dept. of Education, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - D18 Dept. of Labor, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - D19 Diplomas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Di-Dq 19, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Draperies, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Dr-Dz 20, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Ea-En 21, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - E21 Engineering Staff, Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Eo-Ez 22, Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - D18 Deposits N.Y. State Nat'l Bank, Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - F23 Fees-Extension, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - F23 Fees Rules and Regulation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - F23 Fees-Summer Session, Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - F23 Fees-Regular Session, Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Fa-Fk 23, Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Fees- Refunds- S.S. Reg. Extension, Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - F23 Federal Aid, Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Fireman, Undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Fines-Library-Coll. + M.H.S., Undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Fr-Fz 25, Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Fl-Fq 24, Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Ga-Gh 26, Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Gi-Gq 27, Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Gr-Gz 28, Undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Har-Hd 30, Undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - He-Hh 31, Undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Hi-Hn 32, Undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - H33-House, Group Finances, Undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Ho-Ht 33, Undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Hu-Hz 34, Undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - I35 Income Tax, Undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - I35 Injuries To Persons, Undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - I35, Undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - J36 Janitor, Undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - J36 Journal Sheets, Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - J36 Journal Entries, Undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - J36, Undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Ka-Kh 37, Undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Ki-Kq 38, Undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - La-Ld 40, Undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Lab. Fee- Refunds, Undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - L40-Lau's-, Undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Le-Lh 41, Undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Li-Lz 42, Undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Ma-Mb 43, Undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - McA-McD 44, Undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - McE-McK 45, Undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - M47 Additions-M.H.S., Undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - M47 Stage Curtains M.H.S., Undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - M47 New Equip. M.H.S., Undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Me-Mn 47, Undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Mo-Mx 48, Undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - My-Mz 49, Undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Na-Nn 50, Undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - No-Nz 51, Undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - O 52, Undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - O52 Orders-, Undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Pa-Ph 53, Undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - P53 Payroll Information, Undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Pi-Pq 54, Undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - P55 Printing Proofs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Pr-Pz 55, Undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - P55 Printing Contracts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Q 56, Undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - R57 Reports-Annual Press-State-Federal, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Ra-Rh 57, Undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - R57 Dept. Requests, Undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - R57 Retirement-Teachers, Undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - R58 Rockefeller Foundation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Ri-Rof 58, Undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Rog-Rz 59, Undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Sa-Scg 60, Undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - S61 Scholarships-Montgomery Ward, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - S61 Scholarships State, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - S62 Service Ratings, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - She-Shz 63, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - S64- A.D. Simpson-Rulings on all college funds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - S64 Rules Re. Sick Leave, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Si-Sn 64, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - So-Ss 65, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Special Funds, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Salary Standardization, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sta-Sth 66, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - State Aid for Blind Students, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sti-Stz 67, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Student Loan Funds, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Su-Sz 68, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ta-Tn 69, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - To-Tz 70, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Tuition M.H.S., Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - U 71, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ventilation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - V 72, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Wa-Wd 73, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - We-Wg 74, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Wia-Wil 76, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Wim-Wn 77, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Wo-Wy 78, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - X-Y 79, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Billing Materials-VA Old Vouchers, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Reclaim File-VA, 1945-1946; 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Reclaim File-VA, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Reclaim File-VA, 1948-1949; 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-VA, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence-VA, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-VA, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-VA, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-VA, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence-VA, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Paid Vouchers-VA, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Deposits-More than 1 Class Disbursements- More than 1 class, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - AB, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Co-op and Faculty-Student Statements, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - First Trust Company Bank-Statements-Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Glass Board Of Finance Ledger Sheets, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Budget Material, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Budget File, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1942-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Civil Service, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - P55 Power+ Light-Payment Schedule, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - P56 Priority Ratings, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Summer Session, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - M.H.S. Tuition, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Gideon Hawley Equip, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Prohibition, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Financial Report-President's Office, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Income Tax, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Loan Funds, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - National Youth Administration, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Overtime Schedule +Time, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Payroll Information, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Defense Bonds and Pacifism, 1942 February 3 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - File Fingerprints, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - F, Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fee- S.S., Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Dept. Civil Service Payoffs etc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - De, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Career Bill, Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Ce, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Budget Matters, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Band Instruments, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Bequests, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Appropriations, Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Audio Visual Equip. M.H.S., Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Audit + Control, Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Apparatus and Chemicals Chem Dept., Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - American Council on Educators, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Extension Fee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Extension Fee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Extension Fee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Extension Fee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Extension Fee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Budget Data, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Coal, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cafeteria Book-Store, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Carting Coal Etc. Proposal and Specifications, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Engineer & Supt of Buildings, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Diplomas, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Repairs-Alterations To Buildings, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dept. Engineering, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dept. Audit and Control, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Special Services Extension Budget Services, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Special Services Junior College Budget, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Special Services Summer Session Budget, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dept. Employees Retirement, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dept. Taxation and Finance, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dept. Civil Service, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - T.E.R.A. Audit Ed Program, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Tuition- Milne High School, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Still, Permit & Reports. Chemistry Dept., Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - State Aid for Blind, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Special Services Rules & Regulations, Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Summer Session Finances, Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Special Services Regular Budget, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Federal Emergency Work Program, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Fee-Transcript Of Records, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Simpson- A.D., Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Injuries To Persons, Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Income Tax, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Report Annual, 1933-1934; 1934-1935; 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Laboratory Equip. Supplies & Materials, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Landscaping, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Library Book Contracts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Reports-Alcohol, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Reports Annual, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Loan Funds Student, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Leases-Rents, Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Resignations, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Retirement-Teachers, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Report; Presidents Annual etc., 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Rules Re Processing Tax, Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Payroll Information, Undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - T.E.R.A. Student Aid, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Watchman, Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Scholarship-Montgomery Ward, Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Purchase Record Ledger, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Budget and Supplies, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Form F. Fees, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Budget Data and Work Sheets: Special Fees, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Equipment Replacement, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Budget File And Form F, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Budget and Form F, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Schmidt, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - S 61, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Repair Rules Regulating, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Milne High Tuition, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Student Council, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Budget Material, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Reports-Presidents' Annual Unit Costs, information and work sheets, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Payroll, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Payroll, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Payroll, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Payroll, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Payroll, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Budget Dept., 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Budget Material, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 21)